Two hundred and two reais in the bill for those who had nothing.
Bora that this one.
Only day two.
I'll take this here.
Hi all good.
Thanks. It saw
kidney surgery?
Health plan 6 months water 2real
all good brother 2reais caraca the guys want to pay at the pix mano
just to say the pix is too long and I was losing a lot of sale because
the guy is going to send the pix can't send the pix?
And then I made some paper here.
Oh that's tourist code.
You don't have time to pick up the phone.
Take it away man.
Goodnight guys worth bro
And my Band bought up that money break It down girls hit you
Hallelujah girls hit you Hallelujah girls hit you Hallelujah
cause Uptown funk don't give It to you cause Uptown.
Can you send the pix?
Two reais my water you can afford.
Now I'm going to do the accounting for day two bro.
41:35 in cash.
It just got in a lot.
Pix Cara and there's Rolando because I put this
QR code here and people are sending me money.
As you get to their house.
What a dough.
Twenty-eight days left to set up a business.
And that was day two.
Ac me there,
we are with you.